{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947392879492","data":{"timestamp":" 947392879491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 4284e9af-33b2-49ac-821c-b9f458e850c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947392917135","data":{"timestamp":" 947392917135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947392920512","data":{"timestamp":" 947392920512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947392937559","data":{"timestamp":" 947392937559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947392942329","data":{"timestamp":" 947392942329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947392955980","data":{"timestamp":" 947392955980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947392963781","data":{"timestamp":" 947392963781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947392975395","data":{"timestamp":" 947392975394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393004030","data":{"timestamp":" 947393004030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" -"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393013120","data":{"timestamp":" 947393013119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393016387","data":{"timestamp":" 947393016387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393032951","data":{"timestamp":" 947393032950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393042573","data":{"timestamp":" 947393042573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393059758","data":{"timestamp":" 947393059758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074106"," gameId":" 0ee61211-07b0-4209-b7ac-0cf5fa4d4f70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"end":"end"}]}